<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>guide on Noer JP - How to Learn Any Language</title>
    <link>https://noerjp.com/tags/guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in guide on Noer JP - How to Learn Any Language</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:15:32 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://noerjp.com/tags/guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Learn Vocabulary</title>
      <link>https://noerjp.com/posts/mining/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:15:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noerjp.com/posts/mining/</guid>
      <description>So you have your immersion environment. You&amp;rsquo;re ready to plug in and listen to gibberish all day. Great! But how do you actually learn anything?
 Why is this website so vague? It seems to be all theoretical advice! Why won&amp;rsquo;t you give me anything concrete? And why are you so goddamn handsome?
 Patients, my friends. All will be answered in due time.
School Method I remember my first day of Italian class like it was yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Still Can&#39;t Understand は and が</title>
      <link>https://noerjp.com/posts/complexity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 16:09:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noerjp.com/posts/complexity/</guid>
      <description>Preface I am not a qualified linguist nor do I pretend to be. That said, I think I have a pretty compelling explanation, based on experience, as to why the most frequent and basic words in your second language are often the most difficult to wrap your head around.
The Color Spectrum Reality is a lot like color. I&amp;rsquo;m going to sidestep the whole prescriptive vs. descriptive controversy for a moment, but keep in mind what I&amp;rsquo;m about to say is very close to touching that third rail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Should I Watch? Noer&#39;s Official Top Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://noerjp.com/posts/recs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noerjp.com/posts/recs/</guid>
      <description>This isn&amp;rsquo;t as common of a question but I have been asked from time to time. Someone will be onboard with the method and say something like
 Great! I understand how this works now&amp;hellip; but everything is too hard and I have no idea what to watch.
 Which has always been bizarre to me. Just follow your interests. Perhaps a better explanation is needed.
Why You Should Follow Your Interests Listen man, you&amp;rsquo;re gonna have to spend an overwhelming of time in your language to &amp;ldquo;git gud&amp;rdquo; as it were.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why You Should(n&#39;t) Take a Break</title>
      <link>https://noerjp.com/posts/break/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 18:32:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noerjp.com/posts/break/</guid>
      <description>Small Break This past month I have been less active in online immersion learning circles. I&amp;rsquo;ve been absent from Refold, an acquaintances server, and this blog. I&amp;rsquo;ve had a couple major life events happen and as a result didn&amp;rsquo;t have much choice in having to put Japanese to the side. Nothing major happened though and I&amp;rsquo;m fine. I always feared having to take a break but having gone through it I think I&amp;rsquo;ve come away with a new perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re Just a Baby (And Why You Shouldn&#39;t Talk With Natives)</title>
      <link>https://noerjp.com/posts/baby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 11:11:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noerjp.com/posts/baby/</guid>
      <description>Dedicated to Jack This post is dedicated to my friend Jack. I may never be able to convince you of immersion learning, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. It&amp;rsquo;s good blog fuel. This post is basically a letter to him. Taking his main problems with the method as a jumping off point, I am setting out to convince him. My goal is to get him to incorporate immersion.
 Why learn a language?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Immersion?</title>
      <link>https://noerjp.com/posts/what-is-immersion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 15:53:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noerjp.com/posts/what-is-immersion/</guid>
      <description>Confusion There often seems to be confusion about what is meant by immersion. Most people assume it has something to do with living in the country in which your target language is spoken. They assume they need to plan a trip to this country and, after having learned the basics at home, they will magically develop fluency just by being on that country&amp;rsquo;s soil.
Well the good news is that none of that is quite accurate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>START HERE</title>
      <link>https://noerjp.com/posts/start-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 18:05:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noerjp.com/posts/start-here/</guid>
      <description>You want to learn Japanese (or another language). This website is about how to do that effectively.
This website is not a detailed explanation about why that works. (Though there will be some explanation.) For more detail about the point of this website see about.
Who is this for? Friends have asked me how to learn a language. Hi Kyle. Hi Jack. I wanted to put a concise explanation online so people can read it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
