<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>intro-series on Noer JP - How to Learn Any Language</title>
    <link>https://noerjp.com/tags/intro-series/</link>
    <description>Recent content in intro-series on Noer JP - How to Learn Any Language</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:25:28 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://noerjp.com/tags/intro-series/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Start Here</title>
      <link>https://noerjp.com/posts/start-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 18:05:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noerjp.com/posts/start-here/</guid>
      <description>You want to learn Japanese (or another language). This website is about how to do that effectively.
This website is not a detailed explanation about why that works. (Though there will be some explanation.) For more detail about the point of this website see about.
Who is this for? Friends have asked me how to learn a language. Hi Kyle. Hi Jack. I wanted to put a concise explanation online so people can read it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Should I Watch? Noer&#39;s Official Top Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://noerjp.com/posts/recs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noerjp.com/posts/recs/</guid>
      <description>What Should I Watch? This isn&amp;rsquo;t as common of a question but I have been asked from time to time. Someone will be onboard with the method and say something like
 Great! I understand how this works now&amp;hellip; but everything is too hard and I have no idea what to watch.
 Which has always been bizarre to me. Just follow your interests. Perhaps a better explanation is needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Immersion?</title>
      <link>https://noerjp.com/posts/what-is-immersion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 15:53:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noerjp.com/posts/what-is-immersion/</guid>
      <description>Confusion There often seems to be confusion about what is meant by immersion. Most people assume it has something to do with living in the country in which your target language is spoken. They assume they need to plan a trip to this country and, after having learned the basics at home, they will magically develop fluency just by being on that country&amp;rsquo;s soil.
Well the good news is that none of that is quite accurate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
